[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "category": "colours",
      "front": "rosso",
      "back": "red"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "category": "colours",
        "back": "orange",
        "front": "arancione"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "category": "colours",
        "back": "yellow",
        "front": "giallo"
        },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "category": "colours",
        "back": "green",
        "front": "verde"
        },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "category": "colours",
        "back": "blue",
        "front": "blu"
        },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "category": "colours",
        "back": "white",
        "front": "bianco"
        },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "category": "colours",
        "back": "black",
        "front": "nero"
        },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "category": "colours",
        "back": "brown",
        "front": "marrone"
        },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "category": "colours",
        "back": "pink",
        "front": "rosa"
        },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "category": "colours",
        "back": "grey",
        "front": "grigio"
        },
        {
          "id": 11,
          "category": "nature",
          "back": "tree",
          "front": "albero"
        },
          {
          "id": 12,
          "category": "household_items",
          "back": "sedia",
          "front": "chair"
          }
]